Guide to Dean's Office Records Collection RG.051
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- NYU Common Days 2012, 114 Linear Feet (Box 56, Folder 9)
- NYU - Common Days 2011, 114 Linear Feet (Box 56, Folder 10)
- NYU - Common Days - 2010, 114 Linear Feet (Box 56, Folder 11)
- NYU - Common Days 2009, 114 Linear Feet (Box 56, Folder 12)
- NYU Common Days 2008, 114 Linear Feet (Box 56, Folder 13)
- NYU - Continuing & Prof. Studies, 2008-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 57, Folder 1)
- NYU - Courant, 2010-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 57, Folder 2)
- NYU Deans Council, 2011-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 57, Folder 3)
- NYU Deans Meetings 2012, 114 Linear Feet (Box 57, Folder 4)
- NYU - Deans Mtgs. 2011, 114 Linear Feet (Box 57, Folder 5)
- NYU Deans Mtgs. - 2010, 114 Linear Feet (Box 57, Folder 6)
- NYU Deans Mtgs. 2008 - 2009, 114 Linear Feet (Box 57, Folder 7)
- NYU - Executive Committee, 2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 57, Folder 8)
- Faculty of Arts & Sciences, 2009-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 57, Folder 9)
- NYU Finance & R.E. 2012, 114 Linear Feet (Box 57, Folder 10)
- NYU - Finance & R.E. 2011, 114 Linear Feet (Box 57, Folder 11)
- NYU - Finance & R.E. - 2010, 114 Linear Feet (Box 57, Folder 12)
- NYU Finance & R.E. - 2009, 114 Linear Feet (Box 57, Folder 13)
- NYU - Finance & Real Estate 2008 (1), 114 Linear Feet (Box 57, Folder 14)
- NYU - Finance & Real Estate 2008 (2), 114 Linear Feet (Box 57, Folder 15)
- NYU - First Avenue, 2011-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 57, Folder 16)
- NYU - Dick Foley, 2010-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 57, Folder 17)
- NYU Fundraising 2012, 114 Linear Feet (Box 58, Folder 1)
- NYU - Fundraising 2011, 114 Linear Feet (Box 58, Folder 2)
- NYU Fundraising 2006 - 2010, 114 Linear Feet (Box 58, Folder 3)
- NYU - General Counsel, 2009-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 58, Folder 4)
- Genomic Center, 2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 58, Folder 5)
- Grad School of Arts & Science, 2009-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 58, Folder 6)
- NYU - Global 2012, 114 Linear Feet (Box 58, Folder 7)
- NYU - Global 2011, 2011-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 58, Folder 8)
- NYU - Global 2007 - 2010, 2008-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 58, Folder 9)
- NYU - Paul Horn, 2009-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 58, Folder 10)
- NYU - Innovation Venture Fund, 2010-2013; 114 Linear Feet (Box 58, Folder 11)
- NYU Law School (1), 2009-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 58, Folder 12)
- NYU Law School (2), 2006-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 58, Folder 13)
- NYU Press. Office 2008, 2007-2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 59, Folder 1)
- NYU President's Office - 2009, 114 Linear Feet (Box 59, Folder 2)
- US/UK Higher Education, 2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 59, Folder 3)
- NYU President's Office 2012, 114 Linear Feet (Box 59, Folder 4)
- NYU - President's Office 2011, 114 Linear Feet (Box 59, Folder 5)
- NYU - President's Office - 2010, 114 Linear Feet (Box 59, Folder 6)
- NYU - Offsets 2008 - 2009 (1), 2009-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 59, Folder 7)
- NYU - Offsets 2008 - 2009 (2), 114 Linear Feet (Box 59, Folder 8)
- NYU Offsets 2012, 114 Linear Feet (Box 59, Folder 9)
- NYU - Offsets 2011, 114 Linear Feet (Box 59, Folder 10)
- NYU - Offsets - 2010 -, 2010-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 59, Folder 11)
- Rick Matasar, 2012-2013; 114 Linear Feet (Box 59, Folder 12)
- NYU - Medical, 2009-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 59, Folder 13)
- New Education, 2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 59, Folder 14)
- Michael O'Connor, 2011-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 59, Folder 15)
- NYU Provost's Office - 2009 (1), 114 Linear Feet (Box 60, Folder 1)
- NYU Provost's Office - 2009 (2), 114 Linear Feet (Box 60, Folder 2)
- NYU - Provost's Office, 2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 60, Folder 3)
- McLaughlin Monthly Mtgs., 2009-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 60, Folder 4)
- NYU-Meeting Rooms, 2009-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 60, Folder 5)
- Poly Presidential Search, 2011-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Provost's Council on Sci. & Tech., 2011-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 60, Folder 7)
- NYU - Provost - 2010, 114 Linear Feet (Box 60, Folder 8)
- NYU Board 2008 - 2010 (1), 114 Linear Feet (Box 60, Folder 9)
- NYU Board 2008 - 2010 (2), 2008-2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 60, Folder 10)
- NYU - Programs & Projects, 2007; 114 Linear Feet (Box 60, Folder 11)
- NYU Provost's Office 2013, 114 Linear Feet (Box 60, Folder 12)
- NYU Provost's Office 2012, 114 Linear Feet (Box 60, Folder 13)
- NYU - Provost's Office 2011, 114 Linear Feet (Box 60, Folder 14)
- Univer. Relations & Pub. Aff - 2010, 2010-2013; 114 Linear Feet (Box 61, Folder 1)
- NYU-Univ. Relations & Pub. Aff. 2007-2009 (1), 2008-2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 61, Folder 2)
- NYU-Univ. Relations & Pub. Aff. 2007-2009 (2), 2007-2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Dianne Rekow, 2008-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 61, Folder 4)
- NYU - Research, 2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 61, Folder 5)
- NYU - Reynolds (1), 2008-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 61, Folder 6)
- NYU - Reynolds (2), 2007-2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 61, Folder 7)
- NYU Science and Advisory Board, 2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 61, Folder 8)
- NYU - Security, 2008-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 61, Folder 9)
- NYU - Senate, 2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 61, Folder 10)
- K.R. Sreenivasan 2012, 114 Linear Feet (Box 61, Folder 11)
- K.R. Sreenivasan 2011, 2009-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 61, Folder 12)
- NYU - Harvey Stedman, 2009-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 61, Folder 13)
- NYU - Steinhardt School, 2007-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 61, Folder 14)
- NYU - Stern (1), 2010-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 62, Folder 1)
- NYU - Stern (2), 2008-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 62, Folder 2)
- NYU - 2031, 2008-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 62, Folder 3)
- NYU - 2020 Science Initiatives, 2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 62, Folder 4)
- NYU - 2016, 2009-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 62, Folder 5)
- NYU - Student Affairs, 2009-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 62, Folder 6)
- NYU ULT 2012, 2011-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 62, Folder 7)
- NYU ULT - 2013, 114 Linear Feet (Box 62, Folder 8)
- NYU - Tisch School, 2006-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 62, Folder 9)
- NYU - ULT, 2007-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 62, Folder 10)
- NYU - ULT - 2009, 2009-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 62, Folder 11)
- NYU - ULT - 2010, 114 Linear Feet (Box 62, Folder 12)
- NYU - ULT 2011, 114 Linear Feet (Box 62, Folder 13)
- NYU Urban Sustainability (1), 2009-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 62, Folder 14)
- NYU Urban Sustainability (2), 2008-2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 62, Folder 15)
- NYU - Warwick, 2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 62, Folder 16)
- NYU - Wagner, 2008-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 62, Folder 17)
- NYU-Poly Transition 2011 -, 2011-2013; 114 Linear Feet (Box 63, Folder 1)
- NYU/Poly Transition 2007-2010 (1), 2009-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 63, Folder 2)
- NYU/Poly Transition 2007-2010 (2), 2007-2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 63, Folder 3)
- Prospects (1), 2011-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Prospects (2), 2009-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Harold Alexander, 2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Charles DeBenedittis, 2009-2013; 114 Linear Feet (Box 63, Folder 7)
- Kent & Marguerite Charugundla, 2011-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 63, Folder 8)
- Nick Donofrio, 2009-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 63, Folder 9)
- Andrew Economos, 2009-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 63, Folder 10)
- Al Engelberg, 2009-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 63, Folder 11)
- Gregg Fisher, 2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 63, Folder 12)
- Cliff Friedman, 2011-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 63, Folder 13)
- Robert Hillier, 2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 63, Folder 14)
- Ta-Lin Hsu, 2009-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 63, Folder 15)
- Jason Hsuan, 2007-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 63, Folder 16)
- Irwin Jacobs, 2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 63, Folder 17)
- Paul Jacobs, 2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 63, Folder 18)
- Jay Jordan, 2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 63, Folder 19)
- David Lee, 2010-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 63, Folder 20)
- Kent Martin, 2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 63, Folder 21)
- David Mordecai, 2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 63, Folder 22)
- Rho Capital, 2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 63, Folder 23)
- Ron Schilling, 2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 63, Folder 24)
- B.R. Shetty, 2011-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 63, Folder 25)
- Chandrika Tandon, 2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 63, Folder 26)
- Nick Trentacoste (1), 2010-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 63, Folder 27)
- Nick Trentacoste (2), 2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 63, Folder 28)
- Andrew Viterbi, 2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Robin Willner, 2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Ashok Wahi, 2009-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Roger Wang, 2009-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Eugene & Shirley Wu, 2003-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Howard Xia, 2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Ad Hoc Comm. Regents Petition (1), 2008-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 64, Folder 7)
- Ad Hoc Comm. Regents Petition (2), 2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 64, Folder 8)
- Notice of Verified Petition for the Removal of Trustees of Polytechnic Univ., 2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 64, Folder 9)
- Merger Issues - Nov. 2010 -, 2009-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 64, Folder 10)
- Merger Advisory Council, 2007; 114 Linear Feet (Box 64, Folder 11)
- NYU-Poly Merger P.R. Material, 2007-2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 64, Folder 12)
- Due Diligence #3, 2008-2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 64, Folder 13)
- Due Diligence #2 (1), 2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 64, Folder 14)
- Due Diligence #2 (2), 2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 64, Folder 15)
- Agreement & Due Diligence Comm., 2007-2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 65, Folder 1)
- MOU, 2007; 114 Linear Feet (Box 65, Folder 2)
- NYU Merger Regents, 2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 65, Folder 3)
- Attorney General, 2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 65, Folder 4)
- NYU Merger Definitive Agreement, 2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 65, Folder 5)
- NYU - Merger Final Documents, 2008-2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 65, Folder 6)
- LaValle Report, 2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 65, Folder 7)
- Merger Committee, 2007-2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 65, Folder 8)
- NYU Merger Flash Meeting Notes, 2007; 114 Linear Feet (Box 65, Folder 9)
- Alumni Association -2008- (1), 114 Linear Feet (Box 65, Folder 10)
- Alumni Association -2008- (2), 114 Linear Feet (Box 65, Folder 11)
- Alumni Association - 8/07-12/07, 2007-2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Faculty Issues, 2007-2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 66, Folder 2)
- Staff Issues, 2007; 114 Linear Feet (Box 66, Folder 3)
- Student Comments, 2007-2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 66, Folder 4)
- Merger Expenses, 2007-2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 66, Folder 5)
- Merger Town Halls, 2007-2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Trustee Comments, 2007; 114 Linear Feet (Box 66, Folder 7)
- Alumni Comments, 2007-2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 66, Folder 8)
- Process & Comm. 2007-2008, 114 Linear Feet (Box 66, Folder 9)
- Process & Comm. 2006-2007, 114 Linear Feet (Box 66, Folder 10)
- Committee to Save Poly (1), 2008-2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 66, Folder 11)
- Committee to Save Poly (2), 2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 66, Folder 12)
- Merger Discussions, 2004; 114 Linear Feet (Box 66, Folder 13)
- NYU - Poly Merger, 1952-2007; 114 Linear Feet (Box 67, Folder 1)
- NYU-Poly Self-Study Report Vol. III Supporting Documents, 2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 67, Folder 2)
- NYU-Poly Self-Study Report Vol. III Supporting Documents, 2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 67, Folder 3)
- NYU-Poly Self-Study Report Vol. I, 2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 67, Folder 4)
- NYU-Poly Self-Study Report Vol. I, 2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 67, Folder 5)
- NYU-Poly Self-Study Report Vol. II - Part 2 Appendices 3C-5N, 2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 67, Item 1)
- NYU-Poly Self-Study Report Vol. II - Part 2 Appendices 3C-5N, 2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 67, Item 2)
- NYU-Poly Self-Study Report Vol. II - Part 1 Appendices 1A-3B, 2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 67, Item 3)
- NYU-Poly Self-Study Report Vol. II - Part 1 Appendices 1A-3B, 2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 67, Item 4)
- Poly Market-Responsive Strategies, 2007; 114 Linear Feet (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Poly Self-Study Questionnaire for Civil Engineering, 2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 67, Folder 7)
- Poly Response to ABET Draft Statement for Engineering Programs, 2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 67, Item 5)
- Poly ABET Self-Study Report for Chemical and Biological Engineering, 2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 67, Folder 8)
- Poly ABET Self-Study Report for Computer Engineering, 2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 67, Folder 9)
- Poly ABET Self-Study Report for Electrical Engineering, 2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 67, Folder 10)
- Poly ABET Self-Study Report for Mechanical Engineering, 2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 67, Folder 11)
- Poly ABET Self-Study Report Appendix D - Institutional Report, 2014; 114 Linear Feet (Box 68, Folder 1)
- ABET Self-Study Template 2014-2015 Review Cycle, 2013; 114 Linear Feet (Box 68, Folder 2)
- NYU ABET Self-Study Report for Mechanical Engineering, 2014; 114 Linear Feet (Box 68, Folder 3)
- NYU-Poly ABET Self-Study Report for Chemical and Biomolecular Engineering, 2014; 114 Linear Feet (Box 68, Folder 4)
- NYU-Poly ABET Self-Study Report for Civil Engineering, 2014; 114 Linear Feet (Box 68, Folder 5)
- NYU-Poly Manual of Practice, 2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 68, Folder 6)
- NYU-Poly Self-Study Report Vol. II - Part 1 Appendices 1A-3B, 2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 68, Item 1)
- NYU-Poly Self-Study Report Vol. I, 2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 68, Item 2)
- NYU-Poly Self-Study Report Vol. III Supporting Documents, 2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 68, Item 3)
- NYU-Poly Self-Study Report Vol. II - Part 2 Appendices 3C-5N, 2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 68, Item 4)
- ABET Interim Reports - Comments, 2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 68, Folder 7)
- ABET ME Interim Report, 2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 68, Folder 8)
- ABET Computer Engineering Interim Report, undated; 114 Linear Feet (Box 68, Folder 9)
- ABET Electrical Engineering Interim Report, 2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 68, Folder 10)
- NYU-Poly Disaster Recovery and Business Continuation Plan, 2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 68, Item 5)
- NYU-Poly Interim Self-Study Reports, 2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 68, Folder 11)
- NYU-Poly Interim Report on Program Weaknesses and Concerns, 2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 68, Folder 12)
- Self Study: Creating a Useful Process and Report, 2007; 114 Linear Feet (Box 68, Item 6)
- Characteristics of Excellence in Higher Education, 2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 68, Item 7)
- Team Visits: Conducting and Hosting an Evaluation Visit, 2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 68, Item 8)
- Profiles of Engineering and Engineering Technology Colleges, 2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 68, Item 9)